jobscore.com 2019-11-15

# Privacy Policy | JobScore

This privacy policy applies to http://www.jobscore.com owned and operated by JobScore, Inc. (“JobScore”). This privacy policy describes how JobScore collects and uses personal information you provide on our web site http://www.jobscore.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at [ https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request).

JobScore has agreed to notify users of:

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours is collected by JobScore.
  2. How the information is used.
  3. With whom the information may be shared.
  4. How you can access and change your account information.
  5. What security procedures are in place to protect the information collected by JobScore.
  6. How to contact JobScore.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact the JobScore privacy coordinator by e-mail at [privacy@jobscore.com](mailto:privacy@jobscore.com). Any future changes to JobScore’s Privacy Policy will be posted on the JobScore website prior to the changes taking effect. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective. If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should contact JobScore by sending an email to [privacy@jobscore.com](mailto:privacy@jobscore.com).

JobScore complies with the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from Switzerland and European Union member countries. JobScore has certified its adherence to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice; Choice; Accountability for Onward Transfer; Security; Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation; Access; and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view JobScore’s certification page, please visit [ https://www.privacyshield.gov/](https://www.privacyshield.gov/).

## Information JobScore Collects

JobScore collects a wide variety of Information as described in this Section that it uses to provide its membership services and general information services on its website (“Services”). JobScore generally provides Services to two “groups,” Employers and Jobseekers. Each is required to go through an enrollment process in order to use the Services. In doing so, JobScore requires certain information such as your name, address, phone number, email address, job description, resume information, role(s), employment preferences, time zone, and/or credit card information (if you are using a paid-for service). JobScore also collects information related to your overall use of the Services. JobScore also collects information related to discussions, chats, and other correspondence through the JobScore website. We may collect the following personal information from you about your contacts or friends: email address, mailing address, phone number, education history, and job history.

## Information Use

JobScore provides job matching services for Employers and Jobseekers. Employers may use the Services as a way to manage the process of soliciting Jobseekers and managing the hiring process. Jobseekers may use the Services to apply for specific jobs and also to be matched to other potential jobs. For a complete description of the Services, please visit [ www.jobscore.com](http://www.jobscore.com/). We use the information we collect from you about your contacts or friends: to deliver the Services to you whether you are an Employer or Jobseeker, to send you marketing communications when appropriate, to communicate with you about changes to the Services, and to notify you about any changes to our policies and Terms. We also use this collected information to respond to you when you contact us.

## Sharing of Information

The Employer’s job positions and corresponding information will be accessible by anyone through the use of the Services. When an individual applies to a job at a JobScore Network employer, JobScore will share a Jobseeker’s information with the Employer. During the time that a new Jobseeker is under active consideration for a particular position, his/her information will not be generally available for viewing through the Services. After the applicable Employer’s specific job position is no longer considered “active” by JobScore, the Jobseekers that applied to the applicable position will have their data generally available for presentation to other entities that JobScore thinks may have interest in based on collected preference information and system usage patterns. Jobseekers who are already users of the Services prior to the posting of a position by an Employer that they apply for would have their information generally available through the Services regardless of whether they are under active consideration by one or more Employers. If a Jobseeker posts his/her information to the Services outside of a specific position listed by an Employer, the Jobseeker’s information will also generally be available through the use of the Services. JobScore will notify a Jobseeker by e-mail after an Employer has accessed his/her information.

JobScore may also send newsletters and email notifications of promotions or other new information at JobScore and other information that JobScore thinks may be of interest. JobScore will only share your credit card information with a credit card and/or shipping processor for the limited purpose of processing your credit card transaction. Your credit card information is never generally accessible to third parties through the use of the Services. JobScore may also enter into agreements with third parties to assist JobScore with the processing of information and the facilitation of JobScore’s Services. In addition, JobScore may enter into partnerships with third parties that provide products and services related to JobScore’s Services that may be of interest to you (“Partners”) and would therefore share non-financial information with such Partners.

JobScore may also use preference data to tailor your experience at JobScore’s website, showing you content that JobScore thinks you might be interested in, and displaying content according to preferences. JobScore may also use any information it collects to improve the Services. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this privacy policy, JobScore use of information received from Gmail APIs will adhere to [Google’s Limited Use Requirements](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy#additional-requirements-for-specific-api-scopes). JobScore may also use any information it collects from you for summary and statistical purposes and may share the foregoing to third parties, even if an Employer or Jobseeker Opts-Out. The summary and statistical information will not contain any name and contact information.

In cases of onward transfer to third parties of data of EU or Swiss individuals, received pursuant to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield, JobScore is potentially liable.

JobScore takes the privacy of your personal information very seriously. JobScore will not sell, share or rent your information to any third parties except as described in this privacy policy.

## Blogs and Other Public Forums

Our blog is managed by a third party application that may require you to register to post a comment. We do not have access or control of the information posted to the blog. You will need to contact or login into the third party application if you want the personal information that was posted to the comments section removed. To learn how the third party application uses your information, please review their privacy policy. JobScore may also make message boards, chat rooms, user forums, and the like available to its users and visitors. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personally identifying information. To request removal of your personal information from our community forum, contact us at [privacy@jobscore.com](mailto:privacy@jobscore.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

## Information Supplied by Your Browser

JobScore may also log IP addresses for systems administration purposes. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is never shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law.

## Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer’s name. We do obtain the customer’s consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [privacy@jobscore.com](mailto:privacy@jobscore.com).

## Tracking Technologies

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.

We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to support and improve and site operations, functionality and analytics.

We JobScore and our partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level.

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

## Legal Disclaimer

Though JobScore makes every effort to preserve your privacy, JobScore may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, bankruptcy proceedings, or other legal process or if JobScore has a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served on us or (2) protect and defend JobScore’s rights or property. In certain situations, JobScore may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

## Age Restrictions

JobScore’s Services are only intended for persons that are eligible to work under any and all labor laws, rules, and regulations that apply to them, but in no event for persons under the age of 13. By completing any registration and/or otherwise using the Services, you represent that you meet the foregoing requirements. If you do not meet the foregoing requirements, you are not permitted to use the Services.

## Links to Other Websites

JobScore is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites that may be linked to this website.

## Social Media Features and Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## Single Sign-On

For certain Services, you can log in using sign-in services such as an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

## Opt-Out

A Jobseeker may opt-out of receiving further matching opportunities and other communications from JobScore and/or Partners by selecting the applicable do not contact field in his/her account. JobScore will then no longer share your personal information with any Employers and will remove you from and its further communications in accordance with JobScore’s standard removal schedules. Please be aware that if your information has already been shared with an Employer in accordance with this Privacy Policy, that information will remain with the applicable Employer.

An Employer may opt-out of receiving communications and using the Services by sending an e-mail to support@jobscore.com and requesting to no longer use the Services. JobScore shall then make reasonable efforts to forward a copy of the Jobseeker data corresponding to any of the Employer’s job opportunities, in a format determined by JobScore, within 30 days. For the purposes of clarity, JobScore shall continue to have the right to use the foregoing as “Jobseeker data” in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please be aware that if any Jobseeker information has already been shared with JobScore and/or another Employer in accordance with this Privacy Policy, that information will remain with the applicable Employer.

## Correct/Update

Upon request JobScore will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may change or modify certain personal user and enrollment information by login into your user accounts and modifying the applicable information. JobScore will update the information, as applicable, in accordance with JobScore’s standard update schedules. Please be aware that if your information has already been shared with an Employer in accordance with this Privacy Policy, the changed information will not be shared with such Employer.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. Please contact us if you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

## Security

JobScore has reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information stored in JobScore’s database. In order to secure your personal information, access to your account on JobScore is password-protected. In addition, JobScore uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology during your submission of data to JobScore, your access to your account, and any credit card transactions. Although JobScore will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and JobScore’s servers, JobScore cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet. Please be aware that, although we endeavor to provide reasonable security for information we process and maintain, no security system can prevent all potential security breaches. While JobScore strives to protect your Personal Information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online.

## Contacting the Website

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website, or your dealings with the JobScore website, you may send an e-mail to [privacy@jobscore.com](mailto:privacy@jobscore.com), by regular mail at JobScore, 3600 21st Street #203, San Francisco, CA 94114, or by phone at 415-503-9524. If you believe that your (or any) copyright, trademark or other third parties rights have been violated, please notify [legal@jobscore.com](mailto:legal@jobscore.com) and JobScore will investigate.

## Corporate Changes

In the event JobScore merges, sells its assets, or is acquired by another company, information covered by this Privacy Policy would likely be part of the assets transferred to a third party. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. The third party would then have the right to continue using information covered and as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

## Dispute Resolution

In compliance with the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Principles, JobScore commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union and Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact JobScore at [privacy@jobscore.com](mailto:privacy@jobscore.com) by regular mail at JobScore, 3600 21st Street #203, San Francisco, CA 94114, or by phone at 415-904-9900. The enforcement authority that has jurisdiction over JobScore’s LLC compliance with the Privacy Shield is the Federal Trade Commission.

If you do not find the proposed solution satisfactory, JobScore will resolve the dispute under dispute resolution procedures of the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) or the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC) to resolve disputes pursuant to the Privacy Shield Principles. The EU DPAs may be contacted directly via the information provided at [ http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/index_en.htm.](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/index_en.htm) The Swiss FDPIC may be contacted directly via the information provided at <https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/en/home/the-fdpic/task.html>.

Under certain and limited conditions, you may have the possibility to invoke last resort binding arbitration by a “Privacy Shield Panel” composed of at least 20 arbitrators designated by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Commission.

## Acceptance of Privacy Policy

Your use of JobScore’s website, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and the applicable JobScore User Agreement (“Agreement(s)”). BY USING JOBSCORE’S WEBSITE AND/OR THE SERVICES, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE APPLICABLE AGREEMENT. A copy of the Agreements can be found [here](https://www.jobscore.com/agreements/).JobScore reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this webpage. Your continued use of any portion of JobScore’s website and/or the Services following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes. JobScore may enter into additional agreements for use of its Services with its users that have specialized terms (“Private Agreements”). Private Agreements may have unique privacy provisions outside of this Privacy Policy and will be as stated in the applicable Private Agreement with appropriate notice to the data subject.

Effective Date September 20, 2019
